streetunes.com 2011-10-06

# Streetunes - Polytones, Realtones, Wallpapers, Animations. Cool mobile downloads for AT&T,Verizon Wireless,T-mobile and Sprint

At Streetunes, which is operated by SMBP Iglu, Ltd. and its family of companies, we take your privacy seriously. This privacy policy applies to the personal information we collect through this Web site, and describes how we collect, use, disclose, protect, and provide you with access to the personal information about you that we maintain. This privacy policy does not apply to personal information you may otherwise provide to us, or that we may otherwise collect.

### Collection of Personal Information 

Streetunes receives and stores the personal information that you provide on our Web site. The personal information we collect includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, cellular phone number and carrier, e-mail address, and information related to your activity on our Web site. We collect this information from you when you register for our products and services, ask us a question, and initiate other transactions on our Web site. 

### Collection of Other Information 

Streetunes or its agents may collect other non-personal information about your computer (such as your IP address, web browser software, and online activity) when you visit our Web sites. We may also assign you a "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file) that we use for a variety of purposes to enhance your experience on our Web sites. We will provide you with a choice before we collect any personal information through cookies. 

### Use of Personal Information 

Streetunes may use the personal information you provide on our Web sites in certain ways in connection with our business. These uses include: 

  * Providing you with the products and services you request; 
  * Managing your account, including processing bills and handling subscriptions; 
  * Responding to your questions and comments; 
  * Sending you updates regarding the Streetunes charts; 
  * Providing you information about selected products and services that may be of interest to you; 
  * Soliciting information and feedback from you, including through surveys and questionnaires; or 
  * Performing business analyses or for other purposes to improve the quality of our business, our Web site, and the services we offer. 

### Disclosure of Personal Information

Streetunes may share your personal information in limited circumstances, including: 

  * With our authorized service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf (such as to process billing or assist with the transactions you initiate); 
  * To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * When we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or as otherwise required by law; 
  * To protect or defend the rights or property of Streetunes or others, or the safety of the public; 
  * In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale; or 
  * Otherwise pursuant to your consent (for example, when and if we enable subscribers to share with other users lists of the content they have purchased). 

### Access to Personal Information 

You can call us at 1-877-2688110 or e-mail us at support@streetunes.com to update, change, or request that we delete your personal information. 

### Protection of Personal Information 

Streetunes has implemented security procedures to help protect the personal information that you provide to us. However, no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy. 

### Children’s Privacy 

Our Web site is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information. 

### External Links 

If any part of the Streetunes Web site links you to other Web sites, those Web sites do not operate under this privacy policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other Web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information. 

### Changes to This Privacy Policy 

Streetunes may update this privacy policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this privacy policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our Web site. 

### How To Contact Us 

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please call us at 1-877-2688110; or e-mail us at support@streetunes.com. 

* * * This privacy policy is effective as of 20/2/2006.
